(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T21:57:11.467315",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hmmm...
Am I lost again?
This door looks sus...
Should I?
Or should I not?
Dahlah...
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Walk it off and go
Isn't this a thing that you're used to?
Disappointed and feeling blue
When the world doesn't go the way you want it to?
Oh oh
And maybe now is just the perfect time
To let it go and just unwind
There's no need to ask why ever again
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it
Just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh, Dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Walk it off and go
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh, Dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Walk it off and go
What else can you do?
When your feelings are barely there
Up to a point of pure despair
When you have given it your all
But ends in vain
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it
Just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
Let life takes over the wheel
Let life take over the wheel
And shift it to higher gears
Then you will finally see
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
You dont need to be sad
You dont need to be mad
Just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
Dahlah saja, oh Dahlah saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be
Walk it off and go
Dahlah saja, oh Dahlah saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be
Walk it off and go
ma ii ka
Oh well, whatever
Podcast sendiri, ya?
A solo podcast, huh?
Kaelooo~!
Nani?
What?
Apaan, tuh?
What's that?
9 lampu...
9 lights...
Mic... headset...
Content creator?
Eh... Warnanya...
Eh... The colors...
hololive ID?!
Sahabat sejatiku, hilangkah dari ingatanmu
My true friend, has it vanished from your memory?
Di hari kita saling berbagi
Back in the days when we shared everything,
Dengan kotak sejuta mimpi
With a box full of a million dreams?
Aku datang menghampirimu
I came over to see you,
Kuperlihatkan semua hartaku
To show you all my treasures.
Kita slalu berpendapat, kita ini yang terhebat
We always thought that we were the greatest.
Kesombongan di masa muda yang indah
Such arrogance in the beautiful days of our youth.
Aku raja kaupun raja
I was a king, and so were you.
Aku hitam kaupun hitam, arti teman lebih dari sekedar materi
I was dark, and so were you; friendship meant more than material things.
Pegang pundakku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Hold my shoulders, don't ever let go.
Bila ku mulai lelah, lelah dan tak bersinar
When I start to grow tired, tired and losing my shine.
Remas sayapku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Hold onto my wings, don't ever let go.
Bila ku ingin terbang, terbang meninggalkanmu
If I ever want to fly, to fly away and leave you behind.
Ku slalu membanggakanmu
I was always proud of you,
Kaupun slalu menyanjungku, aku dan kamu darah abadi
And you always praised me; you and I are bound by eternal blood.
Demi bermain bersama
Just to play together,
Kita duakan segalanya
We put everything else second.
Merdeka kita, kita merdeka
We were free, we were truly free.
Pegang pundakku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Hold my shoulders, don't ever let go.
Bila ku mulai lelah, lelah dan tak bersinar
When I start to grow tired, tired and losing my shine.
Remas sayapku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Hold onto my wings, don't ever let go.
Bila ku ingin terbang, terbang meninggalkanmu
If I ever want to fly, to fly away and leave you behind.
Tak pernah kita pikirkan ujung perjalanan ini
We never thought about the end of this journey.
Tak usah kita pikirkan ujung perjalanan ini
There's no need to think about the end of this journey.
Dan tak usah kita pikirkan ujung perjalanan ini
And there's no need for us to think about the end of this journey.
Okay... ternyata triknya lumayan gampang.
Okay... turns out the trick is pretty simple.
Jadi ini semacam escape room, ya?
So this is kind of an escape room, huh?
Berarti pintu ini juga dikunci, ya?
Does that mean this door is locked too?
Okay.
Aku harus cari clue di sini biar bisa keluar.
I need to look for clues here so I can escape.
Hmm...
OPEN THIS
ONLY FOR THE WEAK ONES
Ini harus gimana, ya?
What am I supposed to do with this?
Kopi? Kanon? Maksudnya?
Coffee? Cannon? What does that mean?
Hmm...
Masih ada satu kotak lagi sih, tapi aku kan bukan yang lemah...
There's still one more box, but I'm not weak...
Hmm...
Asli nggak paham.
I really don't get it.
Lagian siapa sih yang bakal peduli kalau aku buka yang ini?
Besides, who's going to care if I open this one?
Aku harus buru-buru keluar dari tempat aneh ini, kalau nggak nanti telat 3D showcase...
I need to hurry up and get out of this weird place, or I'll be late for the 3D showcase...
Loncat jalan kiri! Okay, ya udah sana.
Jump, go left! Okay, go over there.
Oke, 1 2 3 loncat! Jalan! Kiri!
Okay, 1 2 3 jump! Go! Left!
Loncat! Jalan! Kanan!
Jump! Go! Right!
Ngapain pula aku lompat? Loncat! Kiri lagi!
Why did I jump anyway? Jump! Left again!
Loncat! Ini yang penting bisa aja! Kiri kiri kiri!
Jump! As long as we can do it! Left, left, left!
Eh? Aku nggak ngerti...
Eh? I don't understand...
Oh! KOPIKANON?!
Ya ampun... clue apaan coba...
Oh gosh... what kind of clue is that...
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets
Temani dalam kesendirianku
Accompanying me in my solitude
Temani aku dalam kepedihan ini
Accompanying me in this pain
Ku bertahan
I endure
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets
Beri semangat baru tuk jiwaku
Giving new spirit to my soul
Beri kicauan merdu tuk hidupku ini
Giving sweet chirps to my life
Ku bertahan
I endure
Aku pasti bisa
I can surely do it
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I am sure I can do it
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets
Beri semangat baru tuk jiwaku
Giving new spirit to my soul
Beri kicauan merdu tuk hidupku ini
Giving sweet chirps to my life
Ku bertahan
I endure
Aku pasti bisa
I can surely do it
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I am sure I can do it
Aku pasti bisa
I can surely do it
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I am sure I can do it
Aku ingin lepaskan
I want to release
Seluruh bebanku
All my burdens
Dan ku jalani hidupku dengan...
And live my life with...
…kan tersenyum.
...will smile.
Aku pasti bisa,
I can definitely do it,
menikmati semua dan mengharapkannya.
enjoying everything and hoping for it.
Aku yakin pasti bisa,
I'm sure I can do it,
dan ku jalani hidupku dengan tersenyum.
and I will live my life with a smile.
Oh, wait...
This room is... different?
Eh? Sleeping.
Does this thing know if I lied? Whatever... sleeping.
Stop asking me the same question! Sleeping! I love sleeping!
Is this some kind of joke? My hobby is anything except answering the same questions over and over again!
Can the door just please open? I've had enough of this.
No, I refuse to answer.
Dahlah.
Fine, whatever.
Oh! Finally a different one, and an easy one too! Eight! Eight, of course, eight!
広い宇宙の 数あるひとつ
In this vast universe, among all the stars,
青い地球の 広い世界で
on this blue Earth in a wide world,
小さな恋の 思いは届く
feelings of a small love reach out
小さな島の あなたのもとへ
to you on a small island.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Meeting you, time flows by.
思いを込めた 手紙も増える
The letters filled with love keep growing.
いつしかふたり 互いに響く
Before we know it, the two of us resonate together,
時に激しく 時に切なく
sometimes fiercely, sometimes poignantly.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Resonating far away into the distance,
優しい歌は 世界を変える
this gentle song changes the world.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the person most important is right by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ
I just want it to reach only you,
届いてほしい 響け恋の歌
I hope it reaches you, echo, love song!
ほら
Look...
響け恋の歌
Echo, love song.
あなたは気づく ふたりは歩く
You realize as the two of us walk,
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
even on a dark path, the moon illuminates our days.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Holding tightly to your hand, never letting go,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
our feelings grow strong, swearing eternity.
永遠の淵 じっと見つめ
Staring intently at the edge of eternity,
それでも足りず 涙に変わり
even so, it's not enough, turning into tears,
喜びになり 言葉にできず
turning into joy, unable to be expressed in words,
ただ抱きしめる ただ抱きしめる
simply holding each other, simply holding each other close.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the person most important is right by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ
I just want it to reach only you,
届いてほしい 響け恋の歌
I hope it reaches you, echo, love song!
ほら
Look...
響け恋の歌
Echo, love song.
夢ならば覚めないで
If this is a dream, don't wake me up.
あなたと過ごした時 永遠の星となる
The time spent with you becomes an eternal star.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the person most important is right by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ
I just want it to reach only you,
響け恋の歌 ほら
Echo, song of love, look...
あなたにとって
To you,
大事な人ほど
the most important person
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
ただあなただけに
I only want it to reach
届いて欲しい
you...
響け恋の歌 ほら
Echo, song of love, look!
ほら
Look,
look,
ほら
響け恋の歌
echo, song of love.
Eh? Ngulang apaan?
Eh? Repeat what?
Chaos?
Kepalaku emang lagi chaos sih, tapi maksudnya?
My head is chaotic right now, but what do you mean?
Meja murid ada 5, terus meja guru ada 1...
There are 5 student desks, and 1 teacher desk...
Aku nggak paham.
I don't get it.
Hmm... Chaos.
Hmmm... Chaos.
Eh?
Hakos Baelz?
Jangan-jangan maksudnya itu?
Could it be that?
JDOONN MY SOULLL!!
Kok pintunya nggak kebuka?
Why isn't the door opening?
Oh, 10 kali!
Oh, 10 times!
Oke.
All right.
JDOONN MY SOUL! 10 kali!
JDOONN MY SOUL! 10 times!
Eh, kayaknya bukan gitu, deh.
Eh, I guess that's not it.
JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL! JDOONN MY SOUL!
Nice!
Wanna be the biggest dreamer 全力で
Wanna be the biggest dreamer, with all your power
未来も今も駆け抜けろ
Run through both the future and the present!
そう僕は気づいたんだ
Yeah, I've realized it
ずっと宿題忘れてただ
That I was always forgetting my homework
それはひとつのナゾナゾナゾ
It's one riddle, riddle, riddle:
「僕は誰なんだろう？」
"Who am I really?"
スライディングしてすりむけたヒザ
My knees that slid and got scraped up
痛くたってね
even if they hurt,
すぐ立ち上がらなきゃ チャンスは逃げてゆく
if I don't stand up right away, the chance will escape.
わかってるさ
I know that already!
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer! 夢見ることがすべて始まり
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer! Dreaming is the start of everything,
それが答えだろ
that's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ飛んでみせるよ
I'll show that I can fly farther than anyone,
すべての明日を貫いて
piercing through all of tomorrow!
地平線まで飛んでいけ
Fly all the way to the horizon,
羽根をもらった勇気たち
our courage that received wings!
強く大きくなるために
To become strong and grow big,
僕も走り出そう
I'll start running too!
聞こえていたよカウントダウン
I could hear it, the countdown,
ずっと前から
from a long time ago.
準備はできてるさ 今すぐ始めよう
I'm all prepared, let's start right now,
ゼロにかわれ！
change into zero!
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer! 信じられなきゃ
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer! If you can't believe,
まばたきしてる刹那に消えるよ
it will vanish in the blink of an eye.
心の標的そらさず走れ
Run without taking your eyes off your heart's target!
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer! 夢見ることがすべて始まり
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer! Dreaming is the start of everything,
それが答えだろ
that's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ飛んでみせるよ
I'll show that I can fly farther than anyone,
すべての明日を貫いて
piercing through all of tomorrow!
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer! 夢見ることがすべてはじまり
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer! Dreaming is how everything starts
それが答えだろ
That's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly farther than anyone
すべての明日を貫いて
Piercing through all of our tomorrows
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer! 夢見ることが
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer! Dreaming is...
すべてはじまり それが答えだろ
...how everything starts, that's the answer, right?
Wanna be the Biggest Dreamer 全速力で
Wanna be the Biggest Dreamer, at full speed
未来も今も駆け抜けろ
Run through both the future and the present!
A bomb now? Okay...
This is getting out of hand already.
I was supposed to be doing my 3D now, but somehow I got lost and trapped in a room with a bomb, and I need to decipher Morse code.
What a fabulous day!
And a phone.
What am I supposed to do?
Call YAGOO and tell him that I'm lost and ask for help?
Wait, I think I know what to do!
Ha- Hello?
I'm lost, and I'm trapped with a bomb.
What?
I hope you can solve Morse code or it's so over.
Huh?
Okay. Dash dot dash dot, dot dot dot dot, dot dash dash dash, dash dash dash, dash dot, dash dot dash dash, dot dash.
C... H... A...
Fast! It's gonna explode!
Can you repeat it again?
Dash dot dash dot, dot dot dot dot, dot dash dash dash, dash dash dash, dash dot, dash dot dash dash, dot dash.
M... O... N... uhm...
What is "CHAMON"?
I think I'm gonna die.
I think the last one is Y... A...
CHAMONYA?
What?
I don't know what you're doing, but good luck!
Thanks! Bye!
Cha- CHAMONYA... Chachamonya?
Chachamonya?
I really wanna be with you, I really really wanna really wanna be with you
You're my love, you're my shine, you're my dear, so trust me, trust me, trust me yeah
そばにいるから
Because I'm by your side
ここに僕がいるから
Because I am right here
Trust me もう何も恐れないで
Trust me, don't be afraid of anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me つながっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
互い感じていて このぬくもり
Feel each other, this warmth
ちゃんと聞こえている
I can clearly hear
君の心の声
the voice of your heart
小さな不安さえ 僕が摘み取ってあげる
I'll pick away even the smallest anxieties for you
何度も伝えたい 君は一人じゃない
I want to tell you again and again, you are not alone
変わることのない 愛はきっとここにある
An unchanging love is surely right here
泣いてみればいい 頼ってみればいい
It's okay to cry, it's okay to rely on me
そのすべてを受け止めると決めた
I've decided to accept all of it
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, no matter where you are
ここにひとつになれる
Here, we can become one
Trust me この思い解けないから
Trust me, because these feelings won't untangle
My dear 変えたりもする
My dear, it can even change things
Trust me 下ろしてみればいい
Trust me, try putting down your burden
そう君のためにも僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for your sake too
Really wanna be with you, trust me, trust me, trust me yeah
どれほどの悲しみ 君は隠してたの
How much sadness were you hiding?
どれほどの思いを 胸に閉じ込めてきたの
How many feelings have you locked away in your heart?
痛みに引き換えに 手に入れた強さを
The strength you gained in exchange for pain...
いつか優しさへ 君は変えていけるはず
You should be able to turn it into kindness someday
奪われたった 壊されたって
Even if it's stolen, even if it's broken
大事なのは 君らしくいること
What's important is staying true to yourself
I'm here たとえ世界が ここに終わるとしても
I'm here, even if the world ends right here
Trust me つないだ手は 離さないから
Trust me, I won't let go of our joined hands
My dear 偽りのない
My dear, with no falsehoods...
Trust me
未来へ
Towards the future,
歩き出そう
let's start walking.
そう 君のために僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for your sake.
I'm here 側にいるから
I'm here, because I'm by your side.
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here.
Trust me もう何も恐れないで
Trust me, don't fear anything anymore.
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread,
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, we are connected.
ただ感じていて この温もり
Just feel this warmth.
いつまでもそばにいる forever
I'll be by your side forever.
いつまでも離れない never ever
We'll never part, never ever.
君がいれば whatever you do
As long as you're here, whatever you do,
ねぇ 僕に教えて whatever you say
Hey, tell me whatever you say.
辛いことあれば すべて飲み込み
If there are painful things, swallow them all.
もしそれでも無理ならば call me
If it's still too much, call me, call me.
You're my love, you're my shine, you're my dear
世界的に回しても trust me
Even if the whole world turns against you, trust me.
Trust me
Yeah baby
泣いてみればいい
You can try crying.
頼ってみればいい
You can try relying on me.
そのすべてを受け止めると決めた
I've decided to accept all of it.
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, no matter where you are.
Call me 一つになれる
Call me, we can become one.
Trust me この思い解けないから
Trust me, these feelings won't unravel.
My dear 抱えた荷物
My dear, the baggage you carry,
Trust me 降ろしてみればいい
Trust me, you can try setting it down.
そう 君のために僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for your sake.
I'm here 側にいるから
I'm here, because I'm by your side.
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here.
Trust me もう何も恐れないで
Trust me, don't fear anything anymore.
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread,
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, we are connected.
ただ感じていて この温もり
Just feel this warmth.
With me もう離れないで
With me, don't leave anymore.
Give me 心を開いて
Give me, open your heart.
Feel me すべてを伝えて
Feel me, convey everything to me.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
With me 言葉はいらない
With me, no words are needed.
Give me 見つめ合えばいい
Give me, just gaze at each other.
Feel me すべてを預けて
Feel me, entrust everything to me.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Trust me yeah baby
Yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah
Hello?
Anybody here?
Okay.
I have played enough horror games, and I don't know why...
but it reminds me of something similar.
Should I read this?
Maybe?
何が目的ですか
"What is your goal?"
なんで居るんですか
"Why are you here?"
キレてますか
"Are you angry?"
怒ってますか
"Are you mad?"
ここに居ていいですか
"Is it okay to be here?"
戻ります
"I'll go back."
帰りましょうか
"Shall we go home?"
戻ろうか
"Should I go back?"
何すればいい
"What should I do?"
何か手伝えますか
"Can I help with something?"
敵意はありますか
"Do you have hostile intent?"
何者ですか
"Who are you?"
どこに居ますか
"Where are you?"
近くに居ますか
"Are you nearby?"
出てきて
"Come out."
アピールしてください
"Please show yourself."
もしもし
"Hello?"
Okay...
That door looks similar to the entrance door.
Is that the exit?
Or is that a trap?
Well, if this is a horror game...
should I try to scream?
AAAAAHHH!
黙れ！
Shut up!
Eh?
そうさ 悲しみを優しさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを力に
and make your true self your strength.
迷いながらでもいい 歩き出して
It's okay to wander, just start walking.
もう一回
One more time.
誰かの期待にずっと応え
Constantly meeting everyone's expectations,
褒められるのが好きなのですか？
do you just like being praised?
なりたい自分をすり替えても
Even if you replace who you want to be,
笑顔はいつでも素敵ですか？
is that smile still wonderful?
始まりだけ夢見て起きる
Dreaming only of the beginning, you wake up.
その先ならいつか
If it's what lies beyond, someday...
自分の腕で
...with your own two hands.
そうだ 大事なものはいつも
That's right, the important things are always...
形のないものだけ
...only the things without a form.
ものだけ
...only formless things.
手に入れても なくしても
Even if obtained or lost,
気付かぬまま
without ever noticing...
そうさ 悲しみを優しさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを力に
turn your true self into strength.
迷いながらでもいい 歩き出して
It's fine to stray along the way, just start walking forward.
もう一回
One more time,
one more time.
ズルい大人は出会うたび
Whenever unfair adults meet us,
頭ごなしな説教だけ
they only give us blunt lectures.
自分を素直に出せなくなって
Unable to express my true self,
傷つけながらすぐに尖って
I got defensive while getting hurt.
新しい風 味方につけて
Taking the fresh wind on my side,
探していいんだ いつか青い鳥を
it's okay to search for that bluebird someday.
そうだ 大事なものは いつも形のないものだけ
That's right, the most important things are always formless.
手に入れても なくしても 気付かぬまま
Even if you obtain them or lose them, you won't notice.
そうさ 悲しみを優しさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを力に
turn your true self into strength.
迷いながらでもいい 歩き出して
It's fine to stray along the way, just start walking forward.
涙の後はなぜか吹っ切れてた
After the tears, somehow I felt a sense of relief.
空に虹が出るように自然なこと
It's as natural as a rainbow appearing in the sky.
雨は上がった
The rain has stopped.
だから 大事なものは いつも形のないものだけ
So the most important things are always formless.
手に入れても なくしても 気付かぬまま
Even if you obtain them or lose them, you won't notice.
そうさ 悲しみを優しさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを力に
turn your true self into strength.
君ならきっとやれる 信じていて
I believe you can surely do it.
もう一回
One more time,
one more time,
もう一回
one more time.
小さな頃には
When I was little,
宝の地図が
a treasure map
頭の中に浮かんでいて
was floating in my head,
いつでも探した
I was always searching
キセキの場所を
for that miraculous place,
知らない誰かに
so I wouldn't lose to
負けないように
someone I didn't know.
今ではホコリだらけの毎日
Now, every day is covered in dust.
いつかの日かすべての
Someday, I'll just entrust
時に身を任せるだけ
myself to all of time.
もしも世界が変わるのなら
If the world were to change,
何も知らない頃の私に
take me back to the me
連れていって
who knew nothing at all,
思い出が色あせないように
so that my memories will never fade.
小さな頃から 歌を歌って
Ever since I was little, I've been singing,
夢見る心 温めてた
warming my dreaming heart.
みんなで真似した 秘密のメロディ
The secret melody we all imitated,
今度は遠くに 聞こえるように
so that this time it can be heard far away.
溜息ついてばかりで 誰もまだ
Doing nothing but sighing, no one yet...
本当の夢さえ 掴めないまま
without even grasping our true dreams.
もしも時代が 巡るのなら
If the times turn around,
見失った頃の 私に
to the time when I lost my way,
連れて行って 拙さが 追い付かないように
take me back, so that clumsiness won't catch up.
もしも世界が 変わるのなら
If the world changes,
何も知らない頃の 私に
to the time when I knew nothing,
連れて行って 思い出が 色褪せないように
take me back, so that memories won't fade away.
連れて行って 切なさが 追い付かないように
take me back, so that sadness won't catch up.
Why does everything feel so real?
Am I real?
Can you even feel my existence?
Is this what déjà vu looks like?
All these memories mean the world to me.
Thank you for walking this journey with me.
Let's make more! :3
like! comments! share! subscribe! :)